afternoon um to everybody in here today.
Thank you everybody uh for being here.
First off, want to welcome uh all of uh
CJ and Adam's family, friends, former
coaches in attendance today. A lot of
our our our great media that covered
Adam and CJ for their career as well as
staff and and others. Um it's clear how
important this day is to the Minnesota
Vikings. Um, and most importantly, a
chance to celebrate two players uh that
have meant so much to the Minnesota
Vikings organization. And as a firsttime
head coach that got a chance to have
these two players on your team, uh you
really don't understand their impact um
until you get into the day-to-day of
getting to have them lead your team,
help uh form the culture that we're all
very proud of in this building and
obviously have a ton to do uh with our
team success. Um I do believe it's
fitting uh that we honor these two
players uh CJ and Adam together uh
today. Um, their journeys are
inspirational,
um, impactful, and and truly great
examples, as as Mark just said, of
something that shows every player, any
player out there. Um, whether it's in
our wonderful state of Minnesota or
anywhere around our country, of uh, the
fact that regardless of your path to the
NFL, anything is truly possible. And
you're able to carve that path by your
hard work, your dedication. You guys are
two of the greatest teammates uh that I
know I can speak for our team and and
many players that you played with over
your time here uh that would say uh your
impact was felt uh on the field for
sure, but in our locker room and in our
community most importantly. Each are
Minnesota natives who actually played
against each other in high school and
college. uh which is uh just a
fascinating thing for two division two
players, rookie mini camp tryyout guys
signed after rookie man rookie mini camp
only to be uh released and put on the
practice squad uh before embarking on
over a decade of of highly impactful
football uh for the Minnesota Vikings uh
earning all pro honors, man of the year
honors, and truly for your home state
team uh being players that uh you know,
all of Minnesota Vikings fans, coaches,
people in this building hold uh in such
in such high regard. I I really do doubt
uh what we're talking about today is
something that has happened before and
and most certainly likely never to
happen again in regards of your journeys
being mirrored in so many ways and and
uh just something we all can be
incredibly uh proud to have had a chance
in my four years here to be around uh
two great players like yourself. CJ Ham,
10 years at fullback, um recording 42
carries for 119 yards, six touchdowns,
84 receptions, 681 yards, and two
touchdowns in 141 career games. Uh but
that's not uh there's no statistic to
measure uh what CJ's impact was uh not
only in the offensive phase of football
um playing the game the right way um
every single day uh but also in the
kicking game phase logging 54 tackles
and a very very impactful uh block punt
uh not too very long ago uh undrafted
free agent like I said out of Augustana
um a four-time team captain and and
really the Pro Bowls that came in 2019
and 2023 three um could have been
mirrored by many many more. Uh if you're
if you're really counting balls and
strikes on playing this game the right
way, uh CJ, you uh you absolutely did
that. Uh he was our team Walter Peyton
man of the year winner uh during each of
his final two seasons here. And um as
the guy that does that vote, I can
promise you guys it wasn't very close.
Um, Adam Thielen, 704 catches, almost
8,500 yards, 64 touchdowns in 13 years
as a receiver uh at the highest level in
the NFL. Undrafted out of Minnesota
State, Mano, he boast he boasts the
second most games played by a Vikings
receiver at 146. And having played golf
with him recently, his body's doing
great um uh to this uh to this very day.
and the third most receiving touchdowns
with 55 in team history. He also ranks
fourth in receptions and fifth in
receiving yards, a two-time Pro Bowl
selection in addition to earning a
second team allpro honor in 2017. And he
was uh our man of the year winner my
first year in 2022 and then proceeded to
go win it again um in Carolina in 2023.
their impacts clearly on and off the
field have left a tremendous impact not
only on myself as the head coach of this
team, all of our players um but also
your families and what you guys were
able to establish in the community uh
here in the Twin Cities and and beyond.
Um I know I today get the opportunity to
speak for not only our team and our
organization, but Minnesota Vikings fans
everywhere, just saying thank you uh for
your impact uh that you guys both had.
With that, it is my honor to bring up
Adam first uh to take some uh questions
and he'll have some remarks uh followed
by CJ Ham. But uh with that, it is my
honor uh to present to you guys Adam
Theling. Give it up for him.
All right.
Good old speech.
Uh yeah, first of all, thanks for
everyone that's in this room. Obviously,
uh, everyone in this room means a lot to
me and thankful for, you know,
everything that you guys have done, uh,
throughout my career and you all know
how that impact is, uh, how where you've
been in that impact and, um, just glad
that you guys are here today. Uh, makes
it extra special for me and CJ. Um, and
to be able to do this with my guy CJ, we
we had an event last night. Um, and did
a little Q&A and and just talking about,
you know, we spent a lot of time
together in this building. Uh, but we've
actually also spent a lot of time
training together outside of this
building. And so, um, fun to be able to
do this with with him and a special
football player and even uh, you know,
better person and somebody who has
really helped shape me even though he's
younger than me. Uh, has has really
mentored me in my faith walk. um as as
an unbelievable example. So, uh good to
do this with you, buddy. Um but yeah,
first of all, just I just want to thank
God. Um Jesus Christ um who kid from
Detroit Lakes, Minnesota is not supposed
to play in the NFL, let alone 13 years
and 11 of those uh with my hometown
team. So, um you know, the the this
platform has been given to me by Jesus.
And I I truly believe for a reason as I
fell through my career uh to be able to,
you know, share that impact and to be
able to give back to a community um and
give back to a kingdom that means so
much to me. So very thankful for that.
Uh for my family, uh for my parents who
uh
um my parents didn't miss a high school
game, uh played four sports, didn't miss
a game. My dad missed one game in
college, my best my best game, and I
give him a hard time for that. Uh but uh
and then been there every step of the
way in in the NFL. Um and my sisters,
their families um have been a huge part
of my my career and my in my walk and
and thankful for them. Uh all the
coaches throughout my career, I wish I
could name you all. Um a bunch are here.
Uh and um all have made an impact in a
different way. Um, I feel bad for my
high school coaches and my middle school
coaches because I was kind of a wild
man. Uh, and my NFL coaches because I
was kind of a wild man there, too. Uh,
but, uh, you know, just the impact that
I mean, I look back at teachers and
coaches, the impact that they made in my
life is is is is so great. I mean, it's
it's unbelievable to look back at. Um, I
remember conversations that I've had uh
in high school just kind of keeping me
in line and and and directing me in the
right path. And um you know it's things
I look at now having three children of
just those mentors just coaches and and
teachers that what what kind of impact
they can have. So very thankful for
that. um you know all the staff um here
in in the building um all the staff
throughout the years of equipment staff,
training room staff, PR staff, community
team um you know there there's so many
people that are outside of the football
staff even, you know, that that make
such an impact in my life and have built
such great relationship with so many of
you in this room. Um that are lifelong
uh relationships that go far beyond the
game of football. Uh so very thankful
for that. All the players I played with,
the relationships, the time that we
spent together and the relationships
that we built. Uh there's nothing
better. And it's the thing I'm going to
miss the most. Um is just being in that
locker room building relationship with
guys that you just you just never know
knew that you would come across and and
build these strong relationships and and
the impact that these guys have made on
me um has really changed my life to be
honest. So, uh, very thankful for all
the players.
Um, the Foundation, Amy, and and Luke
and my agent Blake. Um, uh, thank you
for, you know, all the hard work and
dedication that you put into just
helping me just to be able to not think
about stuff outside of football and my
family and just allowing me to go play
free and and, uh, let you handle all the
hard work. So, thank you guys.
Uh, Minnesota Vikings fans and just the
state of Minnesota in general. Uh,
thanks for just have my back since since
day one. Um, I look back to training
camp, mano, coming from a D2 school,
going back to my school to have training
camp and just the support when I bet
99.999%
of the people didn't think I'd ever uh
play a down of football. Uh, but just
the support that they had coming out,
watching practices, being there to take
pictures, thinking that was probably my
last training camp ever. Um, very
thankful for that.
And this is going to be the hard one.
Um,
this is going to be hard. All right,
Caitlyn, my wife,
so thankful uh for all your support
from day one being at Mano. I remember
coming back and telling you that
that I was going down this journey and
you saying, "I don't know, maybe you
should get a real job."
Uh, I did get a real job. Uh, but a
little bit different than we thought,
but um, just your support, your
dedication, uh, you sticking with me
even when you probably shouldn't have.
Um, and just all that you do outside of
football. I'm so thankful for everything
you've done and who you are as a person
and just you know what your uh you know
who you are as a person and just your
accountability and and just thankful for
that. My kids, I'm so thankful that you
got to see dad play. Um
you guys are great kids and and I'm so
uh thankful to be your dad.
even even you, Hudson.
Uh you guys are special to me and uh I'm
excited to be able to all that support
that you've given me over the years. I'm
excited to turn that back around and
give you guys. So I love you guys. Thank
you. Uh sorry that was too long. I tend
to talk too much as CJ knows. But uh
thank you guys. I didn't think I was
going to cry. I haven't done that in a
long time. But I told CJ the only time I
ever cry is at weddings for some reason.
Uh and uh this is probably the only time
I've ever cried other than that. So,
thank you guys and uh appreciate y'all.
If I cry, I'm going be so mad.
Golly,
why you got to go and do that, Adam?
Adam is
been my guy for a long time. Somebody I
truly appreciate him and his family.
What you've done for for this state, you
did it the right way, man. And I'm glad
to call you a friend, a brother, and we
we locked in for life, brother.
Appreciate you.
Um, for some of the media, you guys
might know, you know, there was a time
in my career where I did these press
conferences pretty often. And, uh, you
know, I I can't do an opening statement
like KO. So, I used to always start with
a dad joke. So, uh, um, your lucky day.
You get another dad joke from me. So,
here we go. Um, what do you call a pony
that has a sore throat?
A little horse.
I got one more. My This just This just
This just This just This just This just
This came to me. One more. One more. One
more. Uh why did Adele cross the road?
>> To say hello from the other side.
All right.
All jokes aside, I mean, Adam was about
to have me start crying, so I had to
start with some jokes. But um
thankful for everybody being here. Um
this is a pretty special day. Um just
filled with gratitude today. And um
every every Saturday before
game day, we would have an optional
mental performance um uh session. And
you know, I think it was the Saturday
before the Seattle game. Um, our mental
performance coach, Matt, asked all of us
to, you know, just close your eyes and
just picture in a circle around you all
the people that have meant the most to
you in your life. Um, you know, taught
you lessons and just been there for you.
And as I close my eyes, many of the
people that are here in this room, uh,
already starting to get emotional. Many
of the people that were here in this
room,
um, were there. So, I'm just filled with
gratitude that I'm able to close this
chapter um of my life with some of the
most important people in my life.
So, I want to start with gratitude
first. I just want to say thank you to
the Vikings organization uh for
believing in me, taking a chance on a
local kid out of Augustana University.
And I mean, to be real, at that time, I
probably had no business being out there
on that field. And um but from day one u
when I walked into this building as a
young player, he gave me the opportunity
to to grow not just as an athlete but as
a man.
I believe this organization is ran the
right way from top to bottom. We've
gotten to work with some unbelievable
people who have helped us, you know,
reach some some goals and some dreams
that we didn't even know that we had.
So, I just want to say thank you to you
guys. You guys know who you are. Um, you
guys mean the absolute world to me.
And the Welsh, I mean, they they care
about winning games, but I think most
importantly, they care about they care
about people. So, I just want to say
thank you to the Vikings organization,
everybody a part of it, for for treating
us like family from from from the
beginning.
To my coaches, past and present. I mean,
I've got coaches here from all different
parts of my journey. And I probably
shared with each of you personally how
much you've mean to me. So, I just want
to echo that today and say thank you for
everything that you've done for me.
Each of you have taught me so much about
the game of football and have pushed me
to my limits to help me be where I am
today. But what I value the most is how
many of you unknowingly taught me so
much more than that. How to be a good
man, a father, a husband, a competitor,
and a friend.
I've been able to lean on many of you
during the hardest times of my life. And
words cannot describe that type of
gratitude. So again, I just want to say
thank you
to my teammates, my brothers, my dog
Adam. I mean, there are there are no
words that can really sum this up, but
this part right here is what I'll miss
miss the most.
That's what I love about this game. It
it can bring so many of us from
completely different backgrounds,
beliefs, upbringings together for
lifelong bonds.
There's there's nothing else like it in
the world. I can tell you that. But what
I really hope is that my teammates know
when I say we're brothers for life that
I mean that from the bottom of my heart.
Whether you're my teammate for a day or
for 10 years, like we are locked in. And
it's it's always been way more about
football. It's been it's been about more
than football.
To my friends that are here, my lifelong
ones, and the ones I've gotten to know
over the years,
thank you for keeping me grounded,
for reminding me that there is more to
life than than the game of football. It
was never just about me as a player, but
always about me as a person.
And the support from each of you has
meant the world to my family and I. And
all of you have been there for us when
we needed you the most. So, I'm forever
grateful for y'all.
and to my family.
I wouldn't be here without you today.
You all have sacrificed so much so I can
chase this dream.
Dang it, Adam. The heck's wrong with
you, dog?
Pops,
from third grade to now, you have made
it a priority in your life to just show
up with a with a camera in hand, as he's
recording this right now.
You are the definition of hard work.
All I ever had to do as a kid was watch
the way that you worked.
And that alone gave me the understanding
that hard work will get you far in life.
Thank you, Pops.
to my mom.
Man, I wish she was here.
The man you see now was first shaped by
her.
Her love, her care, her discipline
plays such a huge role in who I am
today.
The love I have for each person in this
room
comes from her example, which I know
came from her source, Jesus Christ. So,
I love you, Mom. Hope I made you proud.
To my kids, Skyler, Stella, and Trip, I
see you, Stella.
Y'all mean the absolute world to me.
Being your father is the biggest
blessing I could ask for.
Seeing you guys on the sideline before
games was what I look forward to the
most on game days. You guys kept me
going all these years and I know you
will continue to keep me going moving
forward. I'm proud of you guys.
And Steph,
what do I even say?
You are the real superstar of this team.
I firmly believe that I'm not standing
here able to say the words without
everything you've done with done for us.
Whether I was going to be a PE teacher
or NFL player, you're right by my side
supporting me.
The sacrifices you have made
for our family do not go unnoticed.
And there is no way I would have reached
my full potential as a player or as
anything else in this world without you.
The saying goes behind a great behind
every great man as a great woman. And
that couldn't be more true. Thank you.
And lastly, to Vikings Nation, the fans.
Thank you for the best experiences over
these p over this past decade.
There's nothing like game day at the
bank. Adam knows that. KO knows that.
Ain't nothing like it. From the
beginning, I felt all the love. just a
fellow Minnesota kid living his dream of
wearing a purple and gold someday. And I
know that resonated with many Minnesota
fans. So I felt as I was doing it for
doing it for me and my family, I was
also doing it for you. So today, as you
can see, I stand here with a full heart,
tears streaming down my face. I'm so
soft.
Playing 10 seasons for my hometown team
has been nothing short of a dream come
true.
My story up until this point is truly
only something that God can orchestrate.
As I've taken time to reflect, I've seen
God's hand and presence through it all.
My journey is, you know, pretty simple,
pretty pretty much the same as Adam's.
It wasn't pretty by any means,
but I believe that was purposeful in
pointing to God's glory.
Football has meant so much to me since
the age of 11. And as I as I said
before, it taught me so much in life. So
making this decision to walk away from
the game that I love is extremely
difficult.
But as I think about it, the game of
football has taught me to live and play
for something bigger than myself.
And as coach KP would say, do it for
your buddy.
So now standing here looking at my wife,
my kids, my family, my friends,
I truly believe I can say that I'm doing
exactly what the game has taught me.
Choosing to live for something bigger
than myself.
Once a Viking, always a Viking. Skull.
We can jump into questions. You raise
your hand.
>> Um, first of all, congratulations you
guys. Um, I just have a question for
both of you. What went into the
decisions to retire right now? And for
you in particular, Adam, why retire as a
Viking?
Yeah. Um, why retire a Viking? Uh, yeah.
I mean, this place means so much to me.
Um, you know, unfortunately, I didn't
play my entire career here, but, um, but
at the same time, this place is
everything to me. As TJ mentioned, uh,
the Wolves, this organization is is
first class. There's just nothing really
like it. And, um, very thankful to be a
part of it for a long time. Um, and and
also the fact that I I grew up a Vikings
fan, dreamed to play uh for this team.
Uh, I always wanted to be like Chris
Carter and Randy Moss and and Jake Reed
and and and those guys and and so to be
able to retire in my hometown team is is
is such a blessing and so thankful for
that. Um, as far as the decision to to
retire, uh, as CJ said, uh, very
difficult. Um, you know, it's it's
really hard to walk away from this game
on your own terms because you always
feel like you could do more and we've
been wired since we were little kids to
find a way to get better and find a way
to continue to play this game at a high
level. And so really tough. But um I
think um you know at some point um you
know I think there was a point a year
ago even that I I felt a little wore out
um mentally just from from just giving
everything I had every single day for 13
years and beyond that in college and in
high school. uh that it just it was time
and uh excited to see what that next
chapter looks like. To spend that
quality time with my family uh and to be
a stay-at-home full-time dad will be
fun.
>> Um I had a coach that told me he would
only claim me if I played 10 years. So,
um that was that was a big part of my
motivation. Um, all jokes aside, um,
yeah, I just
I just had I just had a piece in my
spirit, um, to wake up and be like, you
know, this it's time and I'm okay with
it. Um, and even this year, you know,
dealing with injuries for the first time
in my life, um, I truly believe it was
it was also God showing me that I'm
going to be okay without football. you
know, not being able to play for six
weeks, I thought it was going to wreck
me and it was hard at first. Um, but as
I leaned in, leaned on my family, I
realized that there there are there are
things out there and I'm going to be
okay. Um, and you know, now it's time to
spend time with my family and uh I love
the game. I feel like I can still play.
Uh, but my spirit is it's good.
>> I think I know the answer, but I'm going
to ask you to get it in your words. When
you look back, is there a moment that
you're going to remember on the on the
cover of the story of your time as a
Viking? What's the what's the picture on
the front?
>> I think just a picture of the locker
room. That's really it. Um I've Adam and
I both have been able to play in some
like really cool games. You know,
Minneapolis Miracle. Um
Buff Buffalo Bills the the fourth and 18
catch. um the largest comeback in NFL
history, like those are all staples,
right? But uh really just the times like
this, sitting next to each other in a
locker room, talking about everything
that's going on in the world, talking
about our faith, talking about our
struggles, talking about what's going
the the good things in our life. Like
those are the things that are just so
hard to replicate. So I think to answer
your question, the picture would just be
me with the boys.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I think I think you just
relationships, right? I mean, exactly
what he said, but you know, I think back
to just all these amazing relationships
that I was able to build over the years
with with so many different people, whe
whether that's players, coaches, staff.
I mean, it it's it's was truly amazing
to just be able to build those
relationships and truly care about so
many people. Uh which is which is hard
because there's a lot of people that
we've you know 90 guys a year, coaches
that change, um staff that change. Like
there's so many relationships, but you
look back at it and you're so thankful
for each and every one of them and
they're real. You know, it's it's you
don't have time to have fake
relationships in this business because
you spend so much time together and and
you're you know, you're not going to
war, but you're going to to battle, you
know, with these guys and and you got to
trust them. And so just the the the true
real relationships as I'd mentioned
earlier um you know the people that have
helped me shape me as a person and
really just held me accountable and and
you know guys like CJ and Kirk Cousins
and Case Keenum those guys like my faith
walk like would not be where I am uh
probably wouldn't be married uh if it
wasn't for those guys. Um and and just
holding me accountable uh teaching me
the right way and and leading me the
right way. So just so thankful for all
those relationships.
>> This is for both of you guys. You've
both been obviously very involved in the
community with your foundations and and
just the work you've done in Minnesota
during your time playing. What does that
look like for each of you now that
you're done in terms of your foundations
and just the the ways you want to be
part of this community as retired
players?
>> Yeah, I'm I'm really excited. Um,
obviously during during your playing
career, you have uh a bigger platform.
Um, probably more opportunity to um, you
know, do some things in the community,
but you don't have the time. Um, so it's
not as hands-on. So, I'm really excited
to just be able to be more hands-on. Um,
really a huge part of the reason why
we're making Minnesota home. Uh,
because, uh, we want to be able to give
back and be around and have be hands-on
in this community that's done so much
for us. I think sometimes if you don't
have anything holding you in a certain
place particularly, you're like, "Oh,
well, we could live anywhere, right?"
And um those are the things that are
like, "Oh, no. Minnesota's home." And
I'm excited to be able to be more
hands-on as a family.
>> I definitely echo that. Um you know, now
the the sky's is the limit. you know, um
there are so many so many great things
we've been able to be a part of with the
help of, you know, IFA and the Vikings
organization to, you know, help us be
able to give the way we want to give and
impact lives. Um but now that we're
done, uh I feel that we can truly be the
hands and feet. Um whatever whatever we
do, we can give our our whole heart to
and actually get out there and do it. Um
and not and not just support from afar.
So, I'm just looking forward to that.
Hey guys, uh just for both of you, you
both were once practice squad players
and obviously became Pro Bowlers in the
NFL. How would you explain what made you
outliers because so many players every
single year get on practice squads,
never make it to have the careers that
you did? Was there one driving force for
you that helped you guys overcome the
odds?
I mean, I think just being willing to do
what's necessary. Um, you know, not not
letting your the thought of what your
purpose is, um, you know, dictate the
way that you move. Um, I think purpose
is truly just being obedient to where
you are and what you have in front of
you. Um, and I think I think for both of
us, you know, as we had to become
special teamers before we even got a
shot, like we both knew like, hey, yes,
we want to be, you know, so and so, you
know, such and such someday, but my
purpose right now is what the coaches
are asking me to do. How can I help this
team? Whether that be special teams, um,
blocking, what, whatever that may be.
So, kind of just taking a seat to your
pride and just living in the purpose um
that you're in right now that's in front
of you that's tangible that that you can
go attack and kind of just hone in
honing in on that. And every year that
changes um you just you just you just
never know. You know, even with with
with with KO um you know, our first year
together, I didn't play a whole lot on
on the offense. You know, we were still
working that out, trying trying to
figure that out. And you know, as the
years gone, like yes, I started playing
more on offense, but then I also had to
find like where does this team need
value? And once I find that, I got to
make sure I do everything in my power to
make sure I'm the person to bring that
value. And we we were able to do that
and, you know, work out work our work
out that way.
>> Yeah, I think I'd add to that.
Obviously, all those things are are are
true. Um, on top of that, I would say
mindset, right? like what what is your
mindset? And it's this this I I call it
a dog mentality like like you you cannot
be denied and I felt like that was that
was where I felt like I had an advantage
over other guys as well. I wasn't going
to be denied and sometimes um you know
sometimes it it maybe came across the
wrong way, whatever, but but it was this
this mentality that every single day I'm
going to prepare so that when it's game
day I don't got to think. I can just go
and and I can have this different
mentality, this little switch that I
could turn on and be a different person.
I always said that when you cross those
lines, like you're not you're not Adam
the dad at home with the kids. Like
you're a different person. You have to
be you have to have a different mindset.
And that mindset can't just be on
Sundays. Like it it it's Wednesday
practice like when everybody else is
maybe going through the motions. like I
treated those like game day and I was
just as mad at a bad play or a drop or
um missed assignment on Wednesday as I
was on game day. And and that was where
I felt like I could separate myself from
others.
>> Um congrats to both of you guys. Uh what
do you want to do dayto-day next? And
Adam, how good can you get at golf?
Uh well um I played golf with KO the
other day and it wasn't good. So I got a
long ways to go. So but uh but yeah
that's
>> I uh let's just say this. I I've never
really taken golf lessons and I've
already had one and I'm about to have
the second one next week. So we're we're
grinding on that. Uh all while the kids
are in school so I'm not taking time
away from the kids. Don't worry. Don't
worry. But um but yeah, and then I think
just dayto-day still trying to figure
that out exactly what that'll look like.
Um but there's some things that I'm
really passionate about and um
definitely want to stay around the game
in some capacity. Um I don't want to
travel all around the country. Uh and
and probably not going to go down that
path with the media and being gone on
the weekends, but um definitely want to
stay around the game. And we'll see what
that looks like as as this uh next few
months go.
Um, I mean, I'm just kind of flying by
the seat of my pants right now. Uh, you
know, um,
just just enjoying life really. Uh, you
know, I was given advice to take one
year for every month that you played.
Um, so 10 months, might as well make it
12 to 12 months and kind of just not to
have any uh, set in stone obligations.
just kind of just be a free agent in
life and uh kind of see where where
where my where my heart gets pulled
towards and I'm excited to go down that
go down that path
>> for both of you guys uh now that this
chapter is over like how much do you
appreciate the parallels that your
journeys kind of intersected and you
guys got to share it as two kids from
Minnesota?
Yeah, I think I think you know we've
talked about a little bit so far, but I
think there's so many things like if if
you just added up the fact that we
played against each other in high
school, that we played against each
other in college, we played with each
other in the NFL, that alone would be
like, yeah, it's it's amazing to look
back on that. But then you add in just
like all the time we spent together off
off seasonason. Like I mean we spent all
this time together during the season and
then we spent all this time together in
the offseason training like trying to
make each other better, trying to not
just better on the football field. Like
we had some amazing conversations in the
offseason that had nothing to do with
football. uh just becoming better men
and better uh husbands and fathers and
being able to kind of share stories and
and struggles, good times, bad times,
all those things. Like he's a lifelong
friend forever. Um and and so you add
that to the whole thing and it's it's a
really special special thing. Um, we're
already doing a few events together like
so we we get to spend more time again uh
as as retired guys and hopefully we'll
get on the basketball court together.
Um, trying to get him to go in the
mornings and he's trying to get me to go
at night. So, we got to get on the same
page there. But, um, but yeah,
definitely uh thankful for our journeys
to cross paths. I mean, who would have
thought when Detroit Lakes was playing
Duth uh that that we'd be playing
together on Sundays. I mean, that's
pretty crazy. Funny note on that. I
think CJ was 250 pounds at that time. Uh
>> 270
>> 270 at that time. And uh I was trying to
tackle him. So that wasn't good. But uh
and I was 155 lbs soaking wet. So um
that was not a good that was not a good
matchup.
>> Um first off, Adam, like
we don't have for the first time in our
lives, we don't have to wake up at 600
7:00 in the morning. So, I'm going to
choose to play basketball at 7:00 p.m.
versus 6:00 a.m. I'm sorry. Um, but no,
I think everything happens for a reason.
And, you know, for our journeys to be so
intertwined, I mean, even our wives
played college soccer in the same
conference and played against each
other, you know, like all those things
happen for a reason. And I I I believe
it was all to show God glory. Um to
reveal um his light and you know who we
serve. Um, I'm just giving all glory to
God on